Friends, if you are sitting at home jobless even after getting a degree, then
ICICI Bank is providing
free training and full time job
opportunity and the best thing is that
you will get money even during the training,
that too a stipend of Rs 18,000 per month, I
swear on mother, and after the training, these people will
give you a full time job whose starting
salary package will be from Rs 4.5 lakh to Rs
5 lakh depending on the location.  BA, BCom,
BSc, BBA, BTech, BCA almost all
degree holders are eligible.  Even MBA
freshers can also apply.  There is
a golden opportunity for those who are jobless and need a job immediately so that they can improve their financial condition.
Because imagine you are getting to work in a bank like ICICI.
Full time job along with training.  You can see that the entire
selection process is transparent.
Selection will be done on the basis of aptitude test and interview.  Watch the video till the end
because you can see on the screen
that this course is Stock Market Made Easy
Course, its price is ₹1000.
You will get this course absolutely free.  For this
I will give you a coupon code which will make this
course 100% free.  And yes,
if you do not want to miss any job or career update,
then
I have given the link of my WhatsApp community channel in the description.
Join that too.
So now let us see how to
apply for this Aspire program of ICICI Bank.
How will the selection take place, what will be the job role.
Everything in step by step detail.
So without any further delay let's get
started.  All right.  So
I have given the link of this program in the description.
ICICI Bank Aspire Program is a training
based hiring program in which they
prepare young graduates and engineers for Relationship Manager basically sales roles.  In this you are
given offline classroom training.  After that,
all India placement is available
in the branch network of ICICI Bank.  This is also a full-time
sales job that requires
direct interaction with customers and field travel.
You can see the location, it is
written All India.  That means, no matter which
state you live in, or which city you live in
, you all can apply.
Experience is 0 to 1 year.  That means even if
you are a complete fresher, you
can apply.  The eligibility is given here below.  Whether you have done
graduation from any stream
or have done engineering, all of you
can apply.  Post graduates and
MBA freshers can also apply for this.
Talking about qualifying marks, you must have at
least 60% marks in both your high school and graduation.
Your age should also be
less than 25 years.  Only then
can you apply for it.  Talking about the program duration,
this training will be of total 2 months.  There will
be offline classroom based training.  If you complete this 2 months training
well then they will
offer you a full time job for the Relationship Manager
job role whose starting salary
is clearly mentioned.  It will be between Rs 4.5 lakh to Rs 5
lakh.  This is CTC and that too
depends on the location whether it will be 4.5 lakh
or 5 lakh.  That means if you divide it, the
salary will be Rs 40 to 45,000 per month,
which is a very good salary for freshers.
Now let's talk about the selection
process, how will you be selected in this
?  So look, it is very easy.  It is clearly written that
your selection will be done in two steps.   The
first step is an online aptitude test.
There will be an online aptitude test in
which questions related to verbal, quantitative, logical
ability, general awareness will be
asked.  If you pass this online
aptitude test then
after that you will have a direct face to face interview.
No HR round,
no technical round.  Simply pass this online aptitude
test and give face to face interview.
This online aptitude test will be
of 85 minutes and there will be no negative
marking in it.  It is a very good
program.  Everything is happening with complete transparency.
Now the doubt that might be
coming in your mind is when will the result of this online test
come?  So see, whenever you submit this test,
after three days the
result will come on your WhatsApp number and your email.
If you pass the result, then
you will get the update of the next step i.e. face to face interview only on email and WhatsApp.
If you have any other doubts related to this program
then you
can read all these FAQs.  Now let me
show you how to apply quickly and
tell you some important points which will
increase your chances of getting shortlisted.   The
link to this program can be found in the description.
Click on the link to
visit the official page of this program.
Scroll down.  The Apply Now button will be
visible here.  Click on this.
Sign in here first.  Enter your mobile number.
Enter OTP and sign in.  After signing in, you have to
enter basic information
about yourself here.  Put a nice
profile photo here and
upload your updated resume here.  Enter your
name etc., graduation details etc. below and
click on proceed.  Done.  Now pay
attention to one thing.  Now you have applied from here.
Now these people will shortlist.
So if your profile, your
resume is shortlisted, then you will have an
online aptitude test.  Then there will be a face to
face interview.  Now let me tell you some
important points.  Look, these
people will shortlist you mainly
on the basis of two things.  First on the basis of your profile photo
and second on the basis of your resume.  So,
use a professional profile photo and a fully updated ATS
friendly resume.  If you do
n't know how to create an ATS-friendly resume,
I'll
link to a video in the description.  Take a look at that video.
If you are jobless then there is a very good
opportunity.  You
can earn a starting salary of Rs 40 to 45,000.  The link
is in the description.  Please apply this.
Now friends, there will be many of you
who will apply
but will not be shortlisted or if they are
shortlisted then they will
fail in aptitude or interview.  So if you
fail, you still have an
opportunity if you are interested in a sales job, then
friends, Tata Stripe
runs a training called
Business Development Executive BFSI,
so you can apply for it.  Look,
Tata STP is run by Tata's trust.
It has 150 centres in 21 states of India.
Their centres are quite good
like private institutes.  These
people provide training on various courses
and provide placement
absolutely free of cost.  You
even get uniform and lunch for free.   The
training at their centres is quite good.
Their placement rate is also quite good.
Such people who have some degree or the other, are
sitting at home jobless, who are interested in doing sales jobs.
For such people,
this course of theirs, Business Development
Executive BFSI, is a very good
course.  After this six week training,
these people will get you a
job in the BFSI industry.  These people will get you placed in BFSI industry i.e.
banking related industry, finance
services and insurance related companies.
Yes,
at most of their institutes, lunch and
uniform are available free of cost.  You will have to make your
own arrangements for accommodation and food.
Any jobless graduate can take this training from them
and get a job through them.
If you are interested in their course
then go directly to the Tata STIPE website.
Click on What We Do here and
scroll all the way down.  Look here you will
find the courses section.  Now here you have to
click on Services Oriented Courses.
After that many types of courses will come.
Here you have to
click on this course Business Development Executive BFSI.
Then all the details of this course will appear here.
See here for centers offering this
course.  So, the names and addresses of all the centres which are offering this course and
where this training is conducted are
coming.
So click on the centre nearest to your home from
where you
want to take this training, its address and the
number of the branch manager there will appear.  You have to
call that number and tell that
you are interested in this course.  When is the
next batch starting?  So they will
tell you that the next batch is starting on this date.
You have to reach a day before.
They take a basic interview
and easily give you admission.
So friends, you also have this option.
First try your best to get yourself included in ICICI Bank
Aspire Program.  If for
any reason it does not happen and you are
interested in doing such sales job then
you should apply for it because the
salary in ICICI is higher.  In this you will get less salary.
Alright friends, now I
give you the bonus gift course.  Look at this, this
is Elon Markets' Stock Market Made Easy
course.  In this, all the
important things of stock market have been taught in a very easy way.
That's why its name is Made
Easy.  The cost of this course is ₹1000.  But if
you use my coupon code EG100 then
this course will become absolutely zero zero.
Meaning you can do this course for free.
You will also get a certificate with this course
and you can see it.  All
important topics are covered.  If
you want to learn stock market then you can do this course.
This course is
designed in both Hindi and English languages.
You will find the link for both in the description
along with the coupon code.  So,
please pick up this gift.  So friends, how did you like the video?   I
hope you got to learn something new from this video.
See you very soon
with another such informative video.  So that's all for now.
Thanks for watching.